Wow! What? Oh, wait!
Yoo-hoo!
Cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha.
Great! Perfect!
I'm like...
This! This is fun!
Good job!
Inimaki!
I was standing in line to see this.
Let's go!
Hello.
I am Mirei Sasaki from Hinashima46.
I am Miku Kanamura.
Today,
Yes, I'm Mihisa Kanemura.
Ta-da!
I'm here at SEGA.
Yay!
If you take a look at our outfit,
you might recognize us.
Yes, you can. We are dressed a bit nostalgically, though,
Today,
Yes.
I'm here to do Love & Berry.
Yay!
We really love Love&Berry,
I'm sure all of you are already here.
You're watching us now like this,
Yes. I love it.
If you loved it.
Yes. My dream came true.
I'm so happy. I'm really happy.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much, SEGA.
I found it in the supermarket that I go to every day,
You found it in the supermarket?
Yes, it was.
It was in the supermarket,
I did it every day.
I did it too.
It's been a while,
I heard I could meet the real Love&Berry,
So, yes, I'm going to have fun.
I'm going to enjoy it.
Let's go!
I don't want to see it.
Yes, I don't want to see. Then let's go in with our eyes closed, eyes closed.
Whoa! I hear a sound. I hear it.
How do you get in?
I'll go in like this.
Okay.
I'm going in like this.
Yes, yes, yes.
Where is it?
I can see it a little. With the camera.
I didn't see it. I didn't see it.
Turn this way.
Like this.
Yes, yes, yes.
Here we go.
I hear it.
Okay, can you see it? Face.
Ready.
Bjahn!
Wow!
I miss it. It's been a long time.
It's been a long time.
Let's go near. Let's go closer.
I didn't know you were this small.
Eh, wait.
Eeeee...
Yoo-hoo.
It's been a long time.
You're so tiny.
Oh, I mean, did we do this standing up?
Did we do it kneeling?
Oh, I was doing it.
I don't kneel.
Probably because I was little.
Oh, I see.
So you must have been pretty spontaneous at this height.
Yeah, I guess so.
Shall we sit down?
Yes, I do.
Wow!
Oh, oh, I touched it!
Hey!
I touched it! It's coming out! Oh, no! Oh, wait, wait, wait! I don't want to see it! What do we do? Ready!
Oh, wait! I'm waiting!
I don't know if I have this! I do, but let me play with it later!
First of all, before we play, I'd like to talk about our Love & Berry Eye!
After all, today, let's start with fashion! Yes, I know!
I love it! Perfect! I mean, it's a berry girl!
I like the pink and black piccis, just like the berry motif! I like the sound of "pizzazz"! I feel nostalgic!
I drew a star here! Oh, you're drawing it? Here! Oh, I drew it! It's so tiny!
I thought for a second that it was a mole, but it's drawn on the tear ducts where the star is! Thank you!
Then, Bread-san's! Yes!
Today's key point is to add color! The sneakers are red, too... Is that it? If I'm not mistaken, it's my lucky color!
My lucky color is red! So... what's the pose?
I'm in the pose I'm in now! Red! It says "red"!
So I put red in it, and did a lot of other things! And blue is in there too,
Blue and red and... today it's blue and it's sparkly! Here, with Miku, I've made it!
I didn't paint it myself! I added the lame stars! Oh, really!
Is it in focus? Oh, it's in focus!
It's in focus! You can see the stars!
We had fun while we were making up! It was fun!
I feel like I'm back in the same heart... I get excited before we play! I have a fever!
I got one just now... but this... I miss it!
I've been playing for a while now, but this one... I miss the old days!
And I get a lot of them! I'm covered!
I get this card again! But it's also nice to have many of them!
I've played so many cards! I've played so many cards! Thank you so much!
I'm new here, but there's a LOVE&Berry convention,
It's probably a small tournament. It's not that big, but I won it!
You were in the LOVE&Berry contest? There were several contestants, like a contest,
I was in kindergarten, so I was a little girl, so I was a little girl. I was probably in kindergarten,
I was probably in kindergarten, so there were some 5th grade girls there, and I won the contest!
I did it every day. Then, I brought that!
Oh! I brought it! Actually, we... we all miss it, don't we?
I brought it here! We used to do this. Look at these cards!
I wanted this case, but I couldn't get it for a long time. It's a box.
I'm falling apart. I miss them so much! Look at this! These stickers and...
I have a lot of them! Mine! The color has changed, but I also have stickers of pukupuku!
I don't want them to be uploaded too often, but... Look!
It's so worn out! It's been used so much... it's already torn off!
But it's a memory! I really used this everyday!
Just a little lighter... my favorite outfit is...
Mihan, this one! Which one? What! Cute!
A dress full of flowers! It's a dress full of flowers!
Look! On the back, I'm probably in kindergarten, and I'm writing "Miren Sasaki"! It's showing.
I wrote it too big... This! It's so cute! That's a Budokai!
I love Budokai! There are so many different kinds of dresses and stuff.
Oh! That's the Budokai course! I'm on the course!
But the dresses are so flattering! I'm so excited!
Really! I love this pastel fruity one! This one, this one is definitely that one!
It's the 109 part! It's like a skein!
Assayou Street! Assessor Street? This is the page, I think!
Oh, yeah! The course where Shibuya wank is waiting for you! Closest to Shibuya! Maybe!
I liked this one too! Genki kiddo hair!
What! Genki koko hair! It's "Genki koko" hair!
You all know this! I do this for everyone!
It's like... Look! Genki koko hair!
I'm sure the kids of this generation know what I'm talking about! Kids of your generation!
You should do this live! Maybe I'll use it! Do you guys get it?
Then look at this! This is the hair of a healthy girl, guys!
What? ! You have so many clothes you don't have, I'm jealous!
Really? Really? And isn't that a lot of clothes, Momi? A lot?
What? ! But I probably don't have this one, or this one, or this one, or this one!
Oh! Really? I already found this tucked in here!
It's called the Winter 2005 Collection List, and I've got all the cards I have right here!
That's great! I'm already a collector!
That was fast! So fast!
Wow! I can smell it from back then!
It's soaked in!
It smells like a video game!
It doesn't smell like video games!
Oh! Can't you smell it? It smells like video games!
Aaah!
Smells like a Love Mary's game!
Is that the smell of cards?
I smell a game!
It brings back memories!
Aaaaah!
I know!
The smell reminds me!
Now that I've said my love to the fullest, I'm going to put it into practice!
Yay!
This is hard work! Like choosing in this way!
What! I know! I don't know, it's been so long!
I have a blank!
It's been a long time!
How many years?
But I'm still the contest champion.
Yes!
That's why I'm so determined!
That's right! You can't lose!
A fight we can't lose!
Yes!
Let's go!
Oh, my God!
It's coming out!
What is it?
Oh! I've got it!
Oh, no! I don't have it!
Would you like a recommendation?
Which one do you recommend?
This one.
I think the difficulty level might be...
I thought you said not to press the pen on this?
Ask him to press the left and right.
Yes!
Ah! What do you want me to do? Stage.
But I also like the street court.
You know, the famous one.
Oh! You sure?
Street Court.
Street court.
Aah! Mixed.
Eh, which one should I choose?
But it's the same as it used to be
Yes, sir.
I'll play with love!
Yoo-hoo! Loveoo!
Stylish
Cute and fashionable
Ah! Oh, here it comes! I get it.
You want cute and fashionable.
It'll tell you your lucky color for the day.
If you press the button...
Oh, no.
It'll kill it.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, I got it.
I didn't do it.
No, I didn't.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Yeah, I've been around.
There are so many people.
Oh, my God, there's people like this.
I want to go so bad.
But there's no way to get out.
I've got it all to myself.
I've got you, Echo's time, purple, purple, purple, purple, purple, purple, purple, purple, purple...
I'm so glad you're here!
I'm in a hurry.
I'll give it a try and see how it reacts.
I'll give it a try and see how it reacts...
I'm still not sure if it's a street card or not.
I wonder if this is the street.
I don't have any booths, and we're running low on staff...
I'm out of it... but I used to be...
I'm not sure if it's a three or a four, but I'm thinking sneakers and hot soles...
Fun, fun, fun!
Scope that sparkle again, and the Keida way tea Iei He caps
Knitting golly one more time, Asa, worsh...
Black, you're up a little
Oh, purple, you don't get it at all!
He told me to hurry and wouldn't give it to him. Which one do you like?
I'm forced to.
But it's low. Lucky you have round balls.
I'm lucky to have a round ball.
I knew you'd be good at this. Golly, you're so much more stylish than me.
A, B, C, D, that's good.
Thank you. That was good.
In Remain. Wow, I used to stand in line to see this.
Let's go. I miss it.
I miss it.
It's so nice because it's twice as big when you enter this dream space.
You're so good!
A, B, C, D.
Not D. Let's step out in one, two, three.
A, B, C, D, you're good to go. One, two, three.
Okay. What do you think of this?
You're a great dancer. It's so hard now that I think about it.
I missed it! I knew it! I'm losing all my fashion power!
I was so happy to see you at the concert.
It's so hard. I was really good at this.
I was really good at this, but your button-pushing is hard to do.
It's so hard, isn't it?
I'm in a hurry, and the time is surprisingly short.
I'll make sure I can get you a Mimpa. I'll help you out.
I don't have a time card, so I'll give you a time card.
Okay, I'll see your card.
I have it, I have it, I don't have it, I don't have it, I'm glad I don't have it
It's great that you can tell by looking at it that you have it I don't know if I have one from this era
2000, recommended, easy. Let's go.
To the purpose. Okay.
I like this Fashion Street I want to go to Fashion Street
This one's in Shibuya, Shibuya is...
Which one?
Love Fashion Street, so I'll go with "Love".
Ei!
Nice to meet you!
I'll make you pretty!
Black! Black? Black?
This one's black, too, this green one.
The green one.
This one? I have this one.
You said you liked the cute ones.
Top to top.
Yes! Yes, yes, yes.
Hi!
Long time no see!
You look good.
What? What's that sound?
What is it?
Oh, no! I'm in a hurry!
Do you have a black one? I don't.
I don't think so.
Oh, this one?
It's not as cute as this one, but I have it in black.
Oh, really? I think I had that one.
Oh, yeah, I've got it.
What do you think?
I think so.
It's so high!
But it's a little below belly.
I'll give it a little more time.
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
What is it?
It's so street fashion.
It's cute and fruity.
It's not the color? It's fashion.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, I want her to wear that too.
Wait, wait, wait...
I got some thick-soled twin sneakers!
Here we go.
I'm going to show you my skills here.
I don't know...
I love "Last Betty"!
I'd love to have you join us!
Mekali, not Rital!
You cry softly, don't you?
I miss you so much!
Even fashionable is no good.
Knock-knock.
Yes!
Yes! Yes!
The secret is in the place
Rhythm is the key
Secrets in place
It's all about the words
Yes!
Oh, no!
Yes! Yes!
Yes!
Any take.
In the results.
Oh no! So hard!
So hard!
Oh, yeah!
This way!
I won!
You're so strong!
Yes!
You can get the second one!
What should I do?
We only got one because we lost.
Seaside or Idol?
I think I'll go for the Idol Stage.
I think I'd like to go to the Idol Stage.
Remember me?
Yay!
Idol Stage is so cute!
You're wearing the cutest clothes, I knew it!
Oh, you're so cute! Merry!
You're so cute!
Wow, what should I do?
I'm gonna dress her a little differently.
Oh, you're so cute.
No way! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
How about this?
It's absolutely adorable.
Is this still okay? I borrowed it from the Japanese.
It's absolutely fine!
Is it?
Oh, my God! This card! Thank you!
Great! Let's do this!
Almost all of them!
All right!
Now all that's left is my button-sniffing
Rhythm, rhythm, rhythm.
Okay, okay.
Oh! Here comes the flap!
Let's play!
It's so hard, isn't it?
It's so hard.
It's hard to find the rhythm.
Next time preview
This part is hard! The rhythm here is so hard!
The music is exquisite...
Yay!
But it's great!
I did it!
I'm so frustrated!
Cute, Sanahi, this outfit is cute!
Oh, my gosh!
I'm so impressed!
Thank you so much!
It's really our youth!
You're the best!
Thank you so much!
You saved us.
It's fun!
Would you like to play against each other?
Oh, we can do that? Is that okay?
We can do it here and here.
Oh, no.
It's already done.
Oh, it's so cute!
It's so cute!
Belly would look great in these.
These are pants.
They look great on you.
They look good on you.
Oh, I fell!
Should I go to Love's?
Yes, you should.
This is too much fun.
Oh, flowers are so much fun!
We made it together.
If you find this video interesting, please like, subscribe to the channel, and comment.
Just like a human being.
To women everywhere
We'll get there
In between my dreams.
Run run run run run, whatever
♪ Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle
It's the same feeling.
What?
Attack Tajima Koregaun and yay!
I did it for the first time I like to play against each other
I could do it
I didn't have any friends, I
Me too, but I've never done this before, almost
So this is how it was done.
Heh.
Thank you for this really valuable opportunity. Really. It's delicious. May we meet again. Our love for Love & Berry will never stop.
High rating and Good button go together. High rating and channel subscription. Subscribe. And finally, the good button. I'm getting a little too serious with this one. One more time.
Please subscribe to the channel and click the "Gut" button. Thank you very much.
Love & Berry